

SHARMIN AKTER

Phone: +8801932069813 +8801932684707

Address: 54/B, North Kafrul, Dhaka Cantonment, Dhaka – 1206

Email: sharminshila9119@gmail.com

OBJECTIVES

To obtain a position closely associated with the knowledge & years of management expertise that has already been acquired in order to enhance a company and further my career. I would like to promote my career in the market leading industry and secure a managerial position with the industry.

CAREER SUMMARY

A growth-oriented with a strong background with to work management, also skilled continuous process improvement as well as performance management, experience in leading team members, high customer service experience. I excellent communication, have leadership and interpersonal skills, people management and problem solving skills which makes work faster, ability to meet deadlines, great attitude towards work and ensure all standards are met in time.

SKILLS

Communication					
Leadership	*	**	**	**	
Problem Solving	*	**	**	**	
Computer		**	•	**	

WORK EXPERIENCE

Minister Hi-Tech Park Ltd. (September 2020 to Present)

Executive (Sales and Marketing)

- Ensure numeric Distribution & appoint new dealer on particular territory
- > Find new opportunity for company products
- > Ensure regular dealer collection and product shifting
- Avail to maintain good communication and follow up with company dealers and partners
- On time reporting to supervisor
- Build a strong relationship with customers

Bijoy International School (March 2019 to April 2020) Senior Teacher

- Determining training needs
- > Dealing with technical issues as management arise
- ➤ Always Monitor the performance of weak students and guide them how to improve
- ➤ Work on cultural program
- Take care of my all students and nursing them properly in daily

Pickaboo.com (September to December 2018) Customer Experience Executive

- Working with operating staff to establish procedures, standards, systems
- > Rectify problems or improve performance
- > Try to research- understanding customer demands
- Recording, analyzing and distributing statistical information
- Dealing with technical issues as customer arise

Bijoy International School (June 2017 to July 2018) Senior Teacher

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration (MBA)

University of Development Alternative

(UODA)

Major: Marketing Result: 3.44 (4)

Year: 2018

Bachelor of Commerce (Hon's)

Mirpur University College

Major: Marketing

Result: 2.87 (4)

Year: 2014

Higher Secondary Certificate (H.S.C)

BAF Shaheen College, Dhaka Subject: Business Studies

CGPA: 4.60 (5) Year: 2009 Secondary School Certificate (S.S.C)

BAF Shaheen College, Dhaka

Subject: Business Studies

CGPA: 4.25 (5)

Year: 2007

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name : Late Md. Moslem Ali Mother's Name : Late Aleya Begum

Date of Birth : Oct 19, 1991

Gender : Female
Marital Status : Married

Nationality : Bangladeshi

Religion : Islam
Height : 5'2"
Blood Group : A+

National ID No : 19912693016001361

Permanent Address : VIL- Vojmohol, P.O - Kakordha, P.S-Bakergonj, District - Barisal Current Location : 54/B, North Kafrul, Dhaka Cantonment, Dhaka, Dhaka – 1206

I hereby certify that all types of information provided above are true and correct to the best of my knowledge and supported by legal documents.

Signature